lugz.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy & Security | Lugz

### Privacy Policy & Security

  * Is my information secure?
  * View the Lugz Privacy Policy

**Is my information secure?**  
Lugz believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our customers. We want you to feel comfortable that personal information such as credit card number will be kept safe throughout your entire shopping experience at Lugz’s Online Store.For added safety we do not store credit card information on our web server. This significantly reduces the chances of Internet credit card fraud. Unfortunately, this also means that on future orders you will have to tell us your credit card information again. We apologize for the inconvenience, but believe the safety benefits warrant this action.It is our policy to never send private information such as your credit card number via email. In fact, this is a policy we recommend you adopt in all of your Internet activities.We designed the Lugz Online Store to accept credit card information only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 3.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator and versions 3.02 or higher of Internet Explorer. This means you’ll be unable to inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection.

**Lugz Privacy Policy**  
Jack Schwartz Shoes, Inc. (“Lugz”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Lugz.com web site.

IP ADDRESS AND COOKIES  
An IP address is a number that is automatically given to your computer when you surf the web. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. Lugz.com collects IP addresses for the purpose of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on Lugz.com. Lugz does not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms and conditions or to protect our service, site, customers, or others.Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Lugz.com will not disclose your personal identifiable information to any third party unless we tell you otherwise when asking for it. However, Lugz.com may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. For example, we might divide Lugz.com’s users into various age groups by percentage. This data is used to customize Lugz.com’s content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.

THIRD PARTY LINKS  
This site contains links to other sites. For example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement, the “click” will take you off the Lugz site and onto other web sites. Lugz is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Please remember that whenever you give out personal information online — for example, via message boards or chat — that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While Lugz strives to protect their users’ personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.

THIRD PARY ADVERTISING  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)

SURVEYS  
Sometimes Lugz.com posts optional surveys in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. The choice is yours – you do not have to answer surveys. If we are asking for optional information, we will mark the required information with an asterisk (*) so you know the unmarked fields are optional and you can skip them if you want.CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES  
Once in awhile, we run contests and sweepstakes on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Sometimes a visitor may be asked to fill out a brief survey in exchange for allowing such visitor to enter the contest or sweepstakes. If we are asking for optional information, we will mark the required information with an asterisk (*) so you know the unmarked fields are optional and you can skip them if you want.

We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and to notify you if you are a winner. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

MESSAGE BOARDS AND CHATS  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

SECURITY  
Lugz.com has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide. We encrypt your personal information, including your credit card number, when transmitting over the Internet using triple key encryption technology via a VeriSign SSL (Secure socket Layer), to safeguard your Internet transactions. VeriSign, Inc. is a leading provider of Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) and digital certificate solutions used by enterprises, Websites and consumers to conduct secure communications and transactions over the Internet and private networks.

CHILDREN  
No information should be submitted to this site by users under the age of 13. Children between 13 and 17 must obtain their parent or guardian’s consent to submit to or post any information at Lugz.com. Users under 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using message boards and chat rooms.

CHOICE/OPT-OUT  
Lugz.com gives users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

Users have the option of removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service by sending an email to [info@lugz.com](mailto:info@lugz.com).

MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION  
Although it is not always possible to remove or modify information, we will make reasonable efforts to do so. If you would like to change or modify information that you previously provided, please send an email your update/corrections to us at [info@lugz.com](mailto:info@lugz.com).

CONTACTING THE WEB SITE.  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact info@lugz.com or you may also send inquiries by mail to:

Privacy Coordinator  
Lugz  
PO Box 545  
Village Station  
New York, NY 10014

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS  
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the Lugz.com’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy or our terms and conditions, please do not use our site. Lugz reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check Lugz.com Privacy Policy for charges each time you use this site.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS  
Please also visit Lugz’s terms and conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the entire Lugz web site.
